ARPIT SRIVASTAVA

o DETAILS ○

Lucknow, India +91-7518297283 arpitsrivstva@gmail.com

○ LINKS ○

Itch.io Profile

LinkedIn

GitHub

∘ SKILLS ∘

C#
C++
Gimp
Adobe Fusion 360
IT Project Management

○ LANGUAGES ○

Hindi English Russian Japanese

• ACHIEVEMENTS •

Top Final Year Project, University

My project was one of the Top Final Year Projects in the University in 2022. I led my team.

https://arpitsrivstva.github.io/Final-Year-Project-Flappy-Bird/

Best Prototype, Touchzing Media

My idea of a casual game through my prototype, was represented by me to the company team and was selected as the best prototype to be worked upon in future.

PROFILE

Built and working on 2D, 3D, WebGL, iOS, Android, Windows, Animation and Offline 2-player games through Unity Engine. Designed Story mode, Board and Arcade games. I love ideating and making Prototypes as well. Currently having 1 year of experience.

Highly eager to play with my skills in a productive space around better people to improve and learn more.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Game Developer at Touchzing Media, Mumbai.

February 2022 — August 2022

- Sampled mobile-based applications on Unity3D/2D with innovative looks and self ideations to finalalize the product for senior developers ahead.
- Made prototypes and used assets given to make unique levels.

(Used Slack for updates, planning and tracking)

Unity Developer (Game Developer) at EventCombo, Jersey City.

September 2022 — January 2023

- Concluded a metaverse project through programming review, editing concepts for further release of the final app.
- Designed levels with modelling samples which increased the aethetic overview of the environment.

(Used Jira for updates, planning and tracking)

EDUCATION

B.Tech., Ajeenkya D.Y. Patil University, Pune.

June 2018 — June 2022

Graduated with High Honors.

★ MY NOTABLE PROJECTS

UnPop it! - A Board Game

WebGL, 2D

(Genres: Soothing, Satisfying, Relaxing Board Game for two.)

Play it on any browser with this link: https://arpitsrivstva.itch.io/unpop-it/

Pop/UnPop the bubbles and enjoy the relaxing game and calm down!

Flappy Birdy Game

2D, PC

Game's Website I built: https://arpitsrivstva.github.io/Final-Year-Project-Flappy-Bird/

(Genres: Hypercasual, Arcade, Retro)

Collect points to maintain the brightness of your screen. My own ideatedversion of the cult game.

Apollo the 13th! - Game Script

Game Design

(Genres: Fantasy, Sci-fi, Educational, Story, Survival, Simulation)

Document file and PPT: https://github.com/arpitsrivstva/My-Apollo-13-Game-Design-Document-and-PPT

This is a **Game Designing** piece which I wrote on the classic movie – Apollo 13 (1995). The movie and project can be made into a big Story Mode Game and it could be a hit among the fans of the movie in an instant.